#### Contact

2102747034 (Mobile) maximino.martell@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/maximino-martell-25749b1b (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

**CCNS** 

**APRN** 

**CCRN** 

## Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Full Professional)

### Certifications

NPI

**CCNS** 

APRN, RN

**CCRN** 

**APRN** 

#### **Publications**

Hemodynamic Monitoring. In M. L. Sole, D. Klein, M. J. Moseley, Introduction to Critical Care Nursing

Electrocardiogram Lead Selection Using Critical Thinking; Concerning Women and Heart Disease and a Case of Wellens Syndrome

## **Maximino Martell**

#### **APRN**

**Greater New Orleans Area** 

## Summary

Advanced Practice Registered Nurse with over 25 years experience in leadership and clinical nursing. Outcome driven clinical practice leader with expertise in communicating corporate vision to optimize evidence based practice and patient outcomes.

Specialties: Board Certified Acute Critical Care Critical Care CNS (CCNS)

## Experience

St Tammany Physicians Network
APRN, Internal Medicine
October 2016 - Present (3 years 9 months)
Covington, Louisiana

## Delta College

Adjunct Faculty LPN Instructor September 2019 - Present (10 months)

Covington, Louisiana

# All American Healthcare APRN

February 2015 - October 2016 (1 year 9 months)

Covington, Louisiana

## Medical Care Center APRN

November 2014 - September 2015 (11 months)

Slidell, Louisiana

### Ochsner Health System

1 year 8 months

Pulmonary/Critical Care APRN
May 2014 - November 2014 (7 months)

new orleans, louisiana

Advanced Practice Clinician Vascular Neurology April 2013 - May 2014 (1 year 2 months)

new orleans, louisiana

San Antonio Military Medical Center Deputy Director, Critical Care Emergency Trauma Nursing July 2011 - June 2013 (2 years)

Ft Sam Houston

**US Army** 

22 years 2 months

Acute and Critical Care Clinical Nurse Specialist May 2009 - June 2013 (4 years 2 months)

Brooke Army Medical Center

Critical Care Registered Nurse May 1991 - August 2011 (20 years 4 months)

University of Phoenix Adjunct Faculty September 2012 - May 2013 (9 months)

MED-ED Nursing Education Speaker March 2012 - May 2013 (1 year 3 months)

## Education

The University of Texas Health Science Center at San Antonio MSN, Advanced Practice Registered Nurse, CCNS, Acute and Critical Care Clinical Nurse Specialist · (2007 - 2009)

Missouri Western State University BS, Nursing Science · (1997 - 2000)